Guide to the William A. Little Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
William A. Little papers
1967-1996
SC1159
Little, William A., 1929-
7.5 Linear feet
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of correspondence and conference files.
Access Terms
Physics--Research.; Physics--Study and teaching.
Collection Contents
- Correspondence
  - Corresp File - Mail Received, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence File (From W.A.L.), 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Mail Received, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - From W.A.L., 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - W.A.L. Correspondence Sent, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - From W.A.L., 1990 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Received by W.A.L., 1984-1987 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - W.A.L. Correspondence Received, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Mail Received, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Conferences
  - CEC Mtg. Columbus, Ohio, 1994-1996 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Cryofuels CEC, 1993-1995 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - CEC Neetubg, 1992 Feb (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - ISHM Hybrid Microelectronics, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - LT 16 Low Temperature Physics, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Institut de la Vie-Theoretical Physics, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - SANIBEL Symposia - Florida Criteria for the Design of an Excitonic Superconductor, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - SANIBEL Symposia - Florida, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - "Les Arcs" - Bourg Saint Maurice-Savoie, France, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - ASC Applied Superconductivity - Tennessee, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Near Zero Conference - Stanford, 1982 April (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Neutral Networks for Computing - Snowbird, UT, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Superc. Electronic Devices, Circuits - NH-Waterville Valley, 1985 August (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Sanibel Symposia - Florida, 1985 March (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Small Particles and Inorganic Clusters - Berlin, W. Germ, 1984 July (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - ERPOS 4-Electrical & Related Properties - Poland, 1984 June-July (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Paper for Italy, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - ICSM-Low DImensional Synthetic Materials - Italy, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Superconductivity (Nature) Boston, 1987 Nov (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Advances in Catalytic Technologies - San Jose, 1987 Oct (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Electrochemical Society - Hawaii, 1987 Oct (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Novel Mechanisms of Superconductivity - Berkeley, 1987 June (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Memory Systems - Paris, France, 1987 June (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - MRS (Materials Research) - Anaheim, CA, 1987 April (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Argonne National Lab. - Physics Colloq. - Illinois, 1987 April (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Sanibel Symposia - Florida, 1987 March (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - High Tc Superconductors - Maryland, 1988 Oct (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Cryocoolers 5 - Monteray, CA, 1988 Aug (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Institut de la Vie - Theoretical Physics - France, 1988 July (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - SEEP 88 Stanford Engineering Executive - Stanford, 1988 June-July (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Basic Technologies for Future Industries - Japan, 1988 March (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - ISTEC Superconductivity - Tokyo, Japan, 1988 March (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Stanford Breakfast Briefings - Stanford, 1988 Nov (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Superconductor Applications - Los Angeles, 1988 Feb (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - IEEE Conference, 1988 Feb (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Stanford Club of LA-luncheon lyceum - Los Angeles, CA, 1988 Jan 28 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Gordon-Superconducting Films - Oxnard, CA, 1988 Jan 11-17 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Cryogenic Mixed Fluids Symposium - Pasadena, CA, 1989 Dec 19 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - DOE - Theory Applied to Materials - Gatlinburg, TN, 1989 Nov 14-16 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Macroscopic Quantum Phenoma - Czechoslovakia, 1989 Sept 18-22 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Cryogenic Engineering UCLA, 1989 July 24-28 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - High Tc Superconductors Stanford, 1989 July 23-28 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - U of British Columbia Spring Colloquium U of BC, 1989 April 20 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Superconductivity - Australia, 1989 Feb 13-14 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - ACS (American Chemical Society) - Dallas, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Paper on NSF, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - New Challenges in Refridgeration - Montreal, Canada, 1991 Aug 10-17 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - APS Meeting Cincinnatti, Ohio, 1991 March 18 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Interagency Meeting on Cryocoolers - Plymouth, Mass., 1990 Oct 24 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Low Temperature Electronics - Berkeley, CA, 1990 April 23-26 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Amsaht's '90 Conference, 1990 April (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Cryogenic Society - State U of NY, 1990 June 17-23 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Material Sci. and High Tc Superconductors - Washington D.C., 1990 April 2-6 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Int Conf on Low Temp Electronics Cryogenics-Berkel., 1990 April 23-26 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Transport Properties of Superconductors Brazil, 1990 April-May (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Applying Superconductivity to Avionics - England, 1990 May 7-8 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - XI Winter Meeting on Low Temperature Phy. - Mexico, 1990 Jan 14-17 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Laboratory Techniques Volume One - W.A. Little, 1982 Aug (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - NBS Conference on Refridgeration for Cryogenic Sensors...Boulder, CO, 1980 Oct (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 2nd Int. Meet on Small Particles and Inorganic Clusters - Switz, 1980 Sept (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - "Internatl. Conf. on Low Dimensional Synthetic Materials", 1980 Aug (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Conferences - Miscellaneous, circa 1985 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Creativity Talk, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Publishing Information North Holland, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Vitaly Lazarevich Ginzburg: Instructions for Writing Paper-in file, 1986 Sept (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Conferences: Preparation for at Stanford (General Information), 1967, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - More Conference Info, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - CEC Stuff, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Jose Mercado, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - C.E.C., 1994 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - ASHRAE, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Grenoble M. Cyrot, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - C.E.C. Albuquerque, 1993 July 12-16 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - APS Meeting: History of Physics, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - SEEP Lecture, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Mittelberg, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Cryogenic Eng Conference, 1992 July (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Laboratory Notebook, 1973-1978 (Box 5, Folder 20)